

Illia Rachkovan

QA Engineer

Linked In - linkedin.com/in/illia-rachkovan-7a54101a2

Email – iliarachkovan@gmail.com

GitHub - https://github.com/IliaRachkovan/Portfolio-Illia-Rachkovan-QA-QC-Manual.git

Mobile - 0938164796

Summary

I Have a good understanding of quality control (QC), quality assurance (QA) processes, requirements, methodology, testing types/approaches, and more. I possess experience in testing web, mobile, and desktop applications, Databases, and APIs. I am also experienced in creating test documentation such as test cases, checklists, test plans, and bug reports. I have strong communication and organization skills, positive, responsible, and flexible person.

Technical skills

Databases

My SQL

Tools and Technologies

- HTML/CSS
- Technical documentation/ SRS
- XML, JSON
- REST API
- Postman
- Fiddler Classic, Fiddler everywhere
- Jira, Mantis
- Git
- TestRail
- Jmeter

Methodologies

• Agile, SCRUM, Kanban, Waterfall

Experience

Company: Adidas

Position: Store manager

Responsibilities: Management

- Organizing all stores processes
- Execution of sales plans by the store
- Monitoring and influence on KPIs affecting the company's sales

- Interviewing and hiring employees
- Teaching and motivating team
- Tracking employees' KPIs
- Cash operations
- Meeting with the management team to discuss the situation in stores and share best practices
- Implementing visual merchandising recommendations

Duration: 2020 – 2022 (2 years)

Achievements: I consider my main achievement to be taking on the challenge of opening a new store for the company I worked for.

In preparation for the opening, I conducted interviews and hired and trained reliable employees who had worked with me for at least one year. I also organized the process of preparing the goods and the visual part of the store in a timely manner.

All the work was completed on time.

After the opening, I organized the store's work and the achievement of business goals.

Company: Adidas

Position: Service consultant, administrator

Responsibilities:

- Working with customers
- Improving store KPIs
- Teaching fellow workers

Duration: 2014 – 2020 (6 years)

Education

- GlobalLogic QA Manual course 2023
- QATestLab online course 2021
- Master in Electromechanical automation systems and electrical drive

Admiral Makarov National University of Shipbuilding

2013-2017

Language

English – Intermediate B2